{
    "subject": "resource/John_Helfrich",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Helfrich",
    "human_readable": "John Helfrich is the primary topic of John Helfrich.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9789773225784302,
            "question": "Who is the primary topic of the text about John Helfrich?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7678395509719849,
            "question": "What is the purpose of the text about John Helfrich?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7638034820556641,
            "question": "Is there information about John Helfrich in the provided text?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7494287490844727,
            "question": "Is there a biographical element to the text about John Helfrich?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.732081413269043,
            "question": "How comprehensive is the information about John Helfrich in the text?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7255778312683105,
            "question": "Who wrote the text about John Helfrich?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6984558701515198,
            "question": "What kind of information might the text about John Helfrich contain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08880100399255753,
            "question": "What is the subject of the text?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.02405264601111412,
            "question": "What can we infer about the content of the text based on its title?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.019988784566521645,
            "question": "Does the text focus on a specific individual?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John Helfrich is the primary topic of John Helfrich.",
            "html": "dbpedia_542_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can we infer about the content of the text based on its title?",
            "html": "dbpedia_542_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the subject of the text?",
            "html": "dbpedia_542_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of information might the text about John Helfrich contain?",
            "html": "dbpedia_542_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_542_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_542_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_542_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_542_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_542_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_542_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_542_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_542_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_542_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_542_57.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can see that there are multiple documents with different topics and information about a person named John Helfrich.\n\nHowever, upon reviewing the documents, I can see that they all mention a person named John Helfrich as the primary topic. Therefore, based on this analysis, I would conclude:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple pieces of information about John Helfrich, indicating that he is indeed the primary topic. This includes his roles as a grandfather, his involvement in community activities (such as dressing up as President Trump), his professional career with NorthWestern Energy, and other details related to his personal life and artistic pursuits."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}